Well, we now have a bit of a dilemma on
our hands. Um, because if we do this, we
aren't actually getting a new array with
the same information. We're just
pointing to the exact same array. So now
what we need to do is basically we would
need to create a new array. So rather
than doing this line, we'd have to say
let B equal a new array. And then I'm
going to manually copy in 1 2 3. But you
probably can see pretty quickly this
wouldn't really work if I was running
the program because what's the point of
um setting it equal to that if
um we're going to have to manually type
it out by hand. So well maybe you
thought of another way to do it. Maybe
you said let's create a new array called
B. We'll set it equal to an empty array
and then we'll loop through everything
in A. So we could say for let item of A
and then we would say B do append or
sorry B.push
item and then there now we will have
taken every item out of A and pushed it
into B. And hopefully you think that
sounds icky to have to write that out
just to copy an array because it is. So
I've got good news for you. Um, the real
solution is very similar to what we just
did here where I said, "Okay, let's
create a new array and then put in one,
two, three. What if there are 100 items?
That's a lot to type." And we may not
know how many items are in the array.
What we could do is we could do what's
called spreading the array, which means
take every item out of the array and
just spread it out and separate them
with commas. So here in B, we can say,
let's take A and spread it out. So the
syntax for that is you do dot dot dot
and then the array you want to spread
out. What this does is it says create a
new array. Inside of that array, I want
you to take every item out of A and copy
it into B. So now what this should do is
now B is pointing to a different array
because we just made a new array here
using the square braces. So it's not
pointing to this any one anymore. Which
means when we make a change here, it
doesn't change B because we copied these
items before we made the change. So if
we save this and go over to our running
code, we get A was originally 1 2 3.
Then we get B was originally 1 2 3. A is
now high 23. B is still 1 2 3. So this
is how you copy information out of an
array into a new copy of an array. So
you create your array. What is A
holding? A is not holding the array.
It's holding information about where
that array is located. So when you make
B, you say, go to where A is located,
take out all of the items where it tells
you, and put them into a new array that
we're going to store in B. And now we've
successfully actually made a second
array that holds the exact same